Um, just real quick, I just want to
touch base on on Chris, um, out of
Missou. Uh, just really excited to get
him. Obviously, um, he was a guy that
was has really, I think, checked a lot
of boxes since the middle of the middle
of the season through the All-Star
process.
um just a guy that the more you watch uh
the more he grew on us and that's
ultimately um you know why we made the
decision to go get him. Uh
big man, good length, he's got a really
good tag. Uh he can do a lot of things.
I think there's a lot of versatility
he's going to be able to bring our
defense. Um so at the end of the day it
was just it was a pretty easy decision.
>> Mil Brian was saying earlier that you
guys had an appetite for like a true
nose tackle. Do you think Chris fits
that mold?
>> He certainly can. Yeah. The the thing I
like most about Chris probably is I said
before the versatility. He can play the
nose. He can play the three. You know,
in some of our our base, some of our big
end stuff, he could do that as well.
He's just one of those guys that I think
is even though he's four years in
college, he's still scratching the
surface a little bit. He was two years
in Florida and then two years at Missou.
You said you liked him more and more the
more you saw him as he went through the
process. Yeah. What were some of the
things that kind of maybe you didn't
notice first glance, but after you saw
him repeated viewings?
>> Yeah, I mean he obviously him playing in
the SEC there's a lot of call it
cross-pollination when you're watching
tape and especially in the second half
of the year. He just seemed to be a guy
that, you know, we're watching an
offense play Missouri and know they had
a bunch of guys, you know, Missou's got
a bunch of guys in their defense in this
year's draft. He just kind of wanted
like who's that guy? Okay. Oh yeah. You
know, it's it so it it's kind of one of
those things that kind of happens
organically if that makes sense. But he
just he just kept checking boxes and he
and he and he rose through the process.
>> There are other big defensive tackles
this spot in the draft. The thing that
stands out with Chris is six sacks last
year. How much did you value the pass
rush capability?
>> You know, when you're splitting hairs
with that, it's certainly something he's
capable of. And obviously, you know, we
talk about the versatility across, you
know, across the roster. His ability to
do that, you know, was part of the
reason, you know, we went up and got
him.
>> Is he ready to play a decent amount of
snaps as a rookie?
>> I mean, it will be that room. I really
like that room right now. I think we all
do. Um, if if [snorts] he's the best
guy, I I fully expect him to be ready to
roll.
>> Milt, I know he only made the one start,
I think, in his two years at Florida.
What did they say about him there?
>> Everything was positive. Uh, from what I
understand, most of that, you know, the
NIL world that we live in and the
opportunity, it was more about the
opportunity at Missou than it was that
he wasn't doing what they wanted him to
be doing at Florida.
>> No, I know obviously Brian's always
going to take the best guy, but you
addressed a couple defensive positions.
How much better do you think you are on
that side of the ball?
see Christmas, you know,
[sighs and gasps] I mean, I obviously
both of these guys are are talented
enough to be drafted where they were and
anytime you can add versatile pieces
with Cece in the secondary and um you
know, with Chris up front, it at the end
of the day, it's created a lot of
competition and that ultimately is
what's going to allow the cream to rise
to the top. Can he help can he be an
instant help with the run defense? That
was kind of Kobe's forte for you.
>> Yeah, I mean I certainly think he you
know he's a big man. You'll see him. I
mean he's broad shoulders, long arms. Um
he certainly you know he c he certainly
can do that. Absolutely.
>> At the combine, Missou's been
represented with players the last few
years.
>> Yeah.
>> What do you like about that program or
their schedule, their competition?
I think what they've done is they've
it's you know we're all trying to find
an identity. Okay, who do we want to be?
I think what they've done at Missou is
they said these are the type of guys we
want to bring in here and they've you
know in the NIL world they've been able
to find those pieces. But I tell you
what, the one thing about those guys
that's a tough group. I mean you can
they're going to play hard and and you
better strap up because they're they're
especially on defense. Um that's the
standard that they've really set the
last few years.
>> What was going on in your room that you
felt you had to jump up those seven
spots?
>> We just really liked him. I mean, uh
there was, you know, we he was a guy
that was that we had on the board at a
spot that it made a lot of sense to go
try to get. And you know, you you know,
we've got a half a doz dozen of us on
the phone with different you know, other
teams. And obviously it it takes a trade
partner. Um and we felt like the value
matched where you know what we were
willing to give up to and
you know you're always playing that you
know you're hedging your bets so to
speak in terms of okay can we wait a
little bit and you know it's a pick is
just a pick until it becomes a player.
And so when we have a player that we
really really liked and an opportunity
went, you know, presented itself to go
get him, that's ultimately what Brian
decided to do.
>> I look at the numbers. I mean, 13 plus
TFLs the last couple years. Just what is
it about him at his size that he can get
in the back field as consistent? I I
think it's partly his length, but he's
he's got a really good first step and
he's got a disruptive way about him that
uh when he presses an edge, he's he can
be, you know, he's hard to handle. So, I
think schematically, he's just one of
those guys that whether you're a true
odd front or you want to play an even
front, you're a multiple front, he's a
guy that can fit, you know, in a variety
of different ways.
>> Is uh medical just a little too much for
you guys?
Um, I don't I'm not going to touch the
medical. Um, at the end of the day, you
know, Chris was Chris was a guy for us.
>> It's obviously different having a draft
without a first round pick. Brian made
it pretty clear at the start of the week
that he wanted to add body to the
corner.
>> Yeah.
>> He had an appetite for a nose.
>> Sure.
>> How good is the feeling where you're at
right now knowing that you've been able
to do both of those things tonight?
>> Yeah. I mean you I'll sleep a lot better
tonight knowing that we've got but and
it's not just about addressing the
position. It's genuinely we got two
young men. I mean Cece is 20 years old.
It's crazy. I feel I feel really old cuz
he's like three months older than my son
in college. So it's just like it's it I
say that to say it's it's not about
addressing the need in the sense that we
got a lot better tonight. if that makes
sense. And the fact that they addressed,
you know, they filled those needs,
that's, you know, that's great.
>> Did you have a sense that the value of
this draft with where you were in this
draft would line up with the needs the
way that they had coming into it?
>> I think I think it has. I mean, and
we're still, you know, we still have uh
day three tomorrow, but there's and some
spots where we would potentially like to
to fill, you know, our roster. The the
board so far so good. Knock on wood is
is is holding up that way too.
>> You know, [snorts] you've you've done
this a long time. Um how often are you
able to marry that need part with the
players that you like? Like you could
have gotten another corner and another
defensive tackle at some point, but
maybe you're not as enamored with them.
>> No. And I it [snorts] I mean I think it
hap it happens a little bit organically
when you're when you realize, okay,
these are some spots we've got to fill.
And then as you're as you're working
horizontally and and stacking the board,
you're going to value potentially a
corner over a, you know, maybe a a
running back, so to speak. But then, you
know, every year of the draft, it's its
own living organism. And some years
it's, you know, you know, you can wait
till later in the draft to pick, you
know, at at a specific position. But at
the end of the day, you know, we'll
we'll see in 3 years how it, you know,
how it all shakes out. But we're really
excited after after today.